/* jshint esversion: 6 */
/* jshint -W033 */

// Questions - Speak Now
export const speakNowQuestions = [

    {
    "question": "You learn my secrets and you figure out why I'm guarded",
    "answers": ["Never Grow Up", "Mine", "Love Story", "Enchanted"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Get me with those green eyes, baby",
    "answers": ["Better than Revenge", "Haunted", "Mean", "Sparks Fly"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "You gave me all your love and all I gave you was goodbye",
    "answers": ["Back to December", "The Story of Us", "Mine", "Speak Now"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Horrified looks from everyone in the room, but I'm only looking at you",
    "answers": ["Innocent", "Speak Now", "Mean", "Long Live"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "And you'll add my name to your long list of traitors",
    "answers": ["Ours", "Superman", "Dear John", "Better than Revenge"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "I bet you got pushed around, somebody made you cold",
    "answers": ["Mean", "Innocent", "Enchanted", "Speak Now"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "But you held your pride like you should have held me",
    "answers": ["Long Live", "Ours", "The Story of Us", "Love Story"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Remember the footsteps, remember the words said",
    "answers": ["Better than Revenge", "Never Grow Up", "Sparks Fly", "Mean"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "The lingering question kept me up 2 AM, who do you love?",
    "answers": ["Enchanted", "Innocent", "Love Story", "Haunted"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "I think her ever present frown is a little troubling",
    "answers": ["Ours", "Mean", "Better than Revenge", "Dear John"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Your string of lights is still bright to me",
    "answers": ["The Story of Us", "Sparks Fly", "Love Story", "Innocent"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Stood there and watched you walk away from everything we had",
    "answers": ["Long Live", "Haunted", "Dear John", "Enchanted"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "And I hope the sun shines and it's a beautiful day and something reminds you you wish you had stayed",
    "answers": ["Ours", "If This was a Movie", "Sparks Fly", "Last Kiss"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "You traded your baseball cap for a crown",
    "answers": ["Superman", "Long Live", "The Story of Us", "Mean"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "The stakes are high, the water's rough",
    "answers": ["Ours", "Love Story", "Innocent", "Back to December"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Now I'm pacing down the hall, chasing down your street",
    "answers": ["Speak Now", "Never Grow Up", "Haunted", "If This was a Movie"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "But I hope someday you'll take me away, and save the day",
    "answers": ["Enchanted", "Ours", "Superman", "Better than Revenge"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Meet me in the pouring rain",
    "answers": ["Sparks Fly", "Haunted", "Speak Now", "Innocent"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "You and I walk a fragile line",
    "answers": ["Last Kiss", "Back to December", "Haunted", "Mean"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "People throw rocks at things that shine",
    "answers": ["Love Story", "Ours", "Mean", "Better than Revenge"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "How the kingdom lights shined just for me and you",
    "answers": ["Innocent", "Mine", "Long Live", "Speak Now"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "I still remember the look on your face, lit through the darkness at 1:58",
    "answers": ["Last Kiss", "Love Story", "Never Grow Up", "Ours"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Now I'm searching the room for an empty seat",
    "answers": ["Long Live", "The Story of Us", "Innocent", "Mean"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "The girl in the dress, cried the whole way home",
    "answers": ["Mine", "Sparks Fly", "Back to December", "Dear John"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Take pictures in your mind of your childhood room",
    "answers": ["Innocent", "Ours", "Never Grow Up", "Haunted"],
    "correct": 2
    },
]